✔ M11 local session re-auth waits seven days and GPS suggestions prefer today's assigned visit (1.4065ms)
✔ M11 syncCaptureSession creates the request route, uploads media, transcribes voice, and maps checklist photo ids (6.7603ms)
✔ M11 syncQueuedSessions marks failed batches for retry and keeps the queue visibly failed until backoff clears (1.8345ms)
✔ M11 airplane-mode job flow syncs after reconnect with conflict flags (15.5081ms)
✔ M11 mobile rejects unassigned cached job writes (0.4733ms)
✔ missing TENANT_ID never bypasses customer-capable persistence safety (0.9637ms)
✔ a named tenant without Firestore fails even when NODE_ENV is test (0.136ms)
✔ memory persistence requires explicit isolated opt-in and rejects normal named tenants (0.2867ms)
✔ system HTTP routes expose sanitized runtime identity and fail unhealthy configuration (20.0582ms)
✔ the composed server can serve an explicitly isolated memory runtime over local HTTP (933.0652ms)
✔ standalone Nexi layout renders exactly one unified composer row (25.7457ms)
✔ standalone Nexi layout does not render unrelated NexOps widgets, a floating FAB, or a permanent greeting by default (1.0386ms)
✔ standalone Nexi sanitizes multiple raw internal error strings (0.2642ms)
✔ standalone Nexi auto-scroll helper only sticks near the bottom (0.2158ms)
✔ standalone Nexi helpers derive display names, hide approval pills, and build conversational phone/maps actions (3.0753ms)
✔ standalone Nexi binds approval replies to the latest visible approval prompt instead of a stale fallback (0.2683ms)
✔ standalone Nexi styling keeps the route-specific bubble, shell, and voice treatments aligned with the live shell (2.083ms)
✔ mobile create fab renders only at the mobile breakpoint (0.7122ms)
✔ mobile create fab points at the shared create menu component (8.004ms)
✔ mobile create fab stays within common phone viewport widths (0.1574ms)
✔ mobile create fab collapses on downward scroll and expands on upward return (0.14ms)
✔ mobile create fab pulse fires once per fresh storage marker (0.1258ms)
✔ mobile create fab hides behind active overlays and keeps shared dismissal rules (0.1761ms)
✔ mobile create fab supports expanded and collapsed render states (0.7249ms)
ℹ tests 24
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 24
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 1995.9416

PHASE_P_HEALTH_MOBILE_A11Y_EXIT_CODE=0
