✔ CRM quote and invoice native schemas parse (2.1039ms)
✔ NativeAdapter exposes CRM read methods (0.8224ms)
✔ native import upserts remain idempotent by legacy CRM external ids (0.5017ms)
✔ NativeAdapter writes native clients and approval-gated quote drafts (1.7526ms)
✔ NexOps 3.2 client records preserve display, billing, and one-way SMS settings (0.6337ms)
✔ CRM read nexi-tools expose pipeline and client lookup (0.9816ms)
✔ CRM clientLookup stays unmatched and never calls a dormant fallback on native misses (0.759ms)
✔ CRM write nexi-tools cover client create, quote draft, catalog/template settings, and invoice reads (17.2903ms)
✔ seeded catalog UTF-8 punctuation survives native settings round-trip (0.6775ms)
✔ CRM createClient tool blocks approval when telephone is missing (0.3981ms)
✔ CRM client route rejects incomplete saves before a client record is created (60.7685ms)
✔ CRM routes read clients created by ApprovalQueue execution from the shared native repository (11.0002ms)
✔ CRM quick payment request routes create minimal ledger-backed invoices from job and client fast paths (17.4939ms)
✔ CRM quote routes create, send, approve, convert, invoice, and renew quotes (56.6066ms)
✔ CRM quote change requests store per-line comments plus a freeform note (9.3068ms)
✔ Quote materialization preserves custom lines and future client-selectable fields (0.4015ms)
✔ Quote terms resolve tenant default, then template override, then per-quote override (0.4854ms)
✔ TECHNICIAN role is blocked from manual quote approval authority (0.4307ms)
✔ NativeAdapter writes invoices and renders invoice PDFs (0.4565ms)
✔ Stripe rail refuses live keys and verifies webhook signatures (0.9923ms)
ℹ tests 20
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 20
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 1151.956
