✔ fielddocs Nexi tools expose property history and recent photos (12.2747ms)
✔ fielddocs Nexi tools generate and fetch visit reports (1.6154ms)
✔ local Nexi chat routes NexCam photo search, property history, and report generation (7.1002ms)
✔ NexDocs tools search unified content and list client folders (59.6548ms)
✔ local Nexi chat can search documents, queue a folder, approve it, queue an upload, and approve it (10.8272ms)
ℹ tests 5
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 5
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 935.2373
