✔ natural-language photo search matches imported metadata (0.9862ms)
✔ vision pipeline stub is wired off by default (0.1935ms)
✔ vision pipeline parses live Anthropic-style JSON responses with usage (1.1381ms)
✔ upload service creates native storage refs, thumbnails, and EXIF metadata (0.7014ms)
✔ before/after pairing and vision fallback are wired (0.3693ms)
✔ leak checklist and report PDF render (2.9115ms)
✔ native repository persists checklists and posted field report records (1.8126ms)
✔ NexCam read tool searches native media repository (0.8957ms)
✔ NexDocs accepts supported uploads, uses a 100 MB cap, and indexes PDF content for search (70.9682ms)
✔ NexDocs keeps a flat folder model and moves each document into only one folder at a time (1.2023ms)
✔ NexDocs unified search returns uploaded docs, office records, and NexCam hits together (3.0636ms)
✔ NexDocs technician fence stays upload-only for destructive management actions (0.3586ms)
ℹ tests 12
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 12
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 914.5145
