✔ live build status is IDLE without durable controller state and fails closed for stale state (0.8536ms)
✔ live build status projects a durable run, warns after 30 minutes without progress, and returns ten newest events (1.4807ms)
✔ deployment evidence is omitted unless it exactly corroborates the live runtime SHA (0.1574ms)
✔ NexCommand provides the required platform-console areas and canonical routes (0.967ms)
✔ NexCommand only displays a sanitized operator error (0.1338ms)
✔ NexCommand exposes managed platform settings, profiles, and roles without treating them as tenant users (0.3591ms)
✔ NexCommand exposes only sanitized staging Gmail provider identity and health (0.1655ms)
✔ NexCommand live build status is durable, refreshes, and exposes controller evidence (0.2586ms)
✔ NexCommand keeps one clean header lockup and removes the duplicate sidebar brand (0.1487ms)
ℹ tests 9
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 9
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 745.1248

FOCUSED_TEST_EXIT_CODE=0
